# Vicente Rubén Borjas Machado

#### **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Birthdate: November 23, 1989

Nationality: Venezuelan Phone: +56 9 7271 3587

E-mail: vrborjasm@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/vrborjasm

Address: Escuela Agrícola,

607F Macul, Chile

#### **RESUME**

I'm a developer and gamer, from Venezuela. Now Living in Santiago de Chile, Chile. With experience front-end and a little in back-end. I am interested in learning new technologies, always trying to follow the best practices of each new language and framework. I enjoy front-end development, and work for good details and a good user experience.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### JUNIOR DEVELOPER

PAYKU | September 2020 - Currently

Front-end development of a platform of payment system using React, redux and Bootstrap.

#### **BENCHMARKING DEVELOPER**

GEPRO | January 2020 - April 2020

Full-stack development of a platform of benchmarking using React, Redux as tools and Material UI, such as back-end development through Node, Express and sequelize.

## **MAINTENANCE ENGINEER**

PONTIFICIA UNIVERSIDAD CATOLICA DE CHILE | 2018 - 2020

Preparation and coordination of maintenance plans for the equipment found in the teaching laboratories of the Faculty of Physics, development of small applications to improve the control and order of the laboratory equipment.

## **EDUCATION**

## **COMPUTER PROGRAMMING ENGINEER**

Professional Institute AIEP | Santiago, Chile March 2019 - Currently

#### **ELECTRICAL ENGINEER**

Universidad Central de Venezuela | Caracas, Venezuela July 2009 - April 2017

#### **SKILLS**

## **GENERAL**

- Responsibility
- Efficient communication
- · Ability to Work in a Team
- Puntuality
- Autodidact
- Adaptability
- Critical thinking

## **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

- HTML
- CSS
- ES6+/JavaScript

#### **TOOLS**

- Git
- npm
- Bootstrap
- Foundation
- React
- NextJS
- Redux
- Firebase
- Material UI
- Ruby on Rails
- Node JS
- Express
- Sequelize

## **LANGUAGES**

- Native Spanish
- English Advance Level
- Portugues Medium Level